TRISTON BURNS

• Tucson, Arizona 85658 •

• Phone: (520)405-3987 | Email: tristonburns97@gmail.com •

• Github:https://github.com/tbsvl | Portfolio: https://tcb-react-portfolio.herokuapp.com • LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/triston-burns-324499209/ •

SUMMARY

Ambitious Full-Stack Web Developer with a background in data analytics that builds and designs engaging client-side experiences. Received a certificate in Full-Stack Development from the University of Arizona. Works with a collaborative team introducing new ideas with the world to always strengthen problem solving skills.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: JavaScript, HTML, CSS, SQL, Python, Node.js

Applications: React, Bootstrap, Github, MySQL, Express.js, Mongoose

PROJECTS

GedditDone | Github: https://github.com/tbsdvl/GedditDone |

Link: https://gedditdone.herokuapp.com

- GedditDone is a job posting app that connects employers and job seekers. Job seekers may sign up and create a post that offers their services at competitive costs.
- Designed wireframe, developed website views with templating tools, coded stylesheets
- Node.js, Handlebars.js, HTML, CSS

Note Taker | Github: https://github.com/tbsdvl/NoteTaker | Link: https://mynotetakertcb.herokuapp.com

- A note taking app that allows users to add text & save important notes to a bulletin.
- Code backend logic such as building GET & POST routes to the app's API.
- Node.js, Express.js, MySQL

Employee Tracker | Github: https://github.com/tbsdvl/EmployeeTracker

- This application allows a user to interact with an employee database.
- · Code database with MySQL, develop user interface with JavaScript
- Node.js, MySQL, Inquirer

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Verde Brewing Company

January 2020 - May 2020

Data Analyst

- Analyzed sales data with Pandas to develop seasonal beverage preferences for 300+ customers
- Analyzed production data to optimize manufacturing process to 15 cans per minute

Acralight Solar, Tucson, AZ

May 2011 - July 2016

MIS Technician

- Worked with MIS department to design database including 7 different departments
- Provided database management across 7 departments
- Developed company home website increasing online consumer orders 15%

EDUCATION

Bootcamp Certificate • University of Arizona, Tucson, AZ • February 2021 - May 2021

Barrett Honors College • BS Business Data Analytics • August 2016 - May 2020